Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
Beishan.
بيشان.
Beishan,
بيشان،
Qingwan is back.
لقد عاد تشينغوان.
Madam, what's wrong with you?
سيدتي، ما الذي حدث لك؟
Why would a performer be Qingwan?
لماذا يكون المؤدي تشينغوان؟
You gave this jade pendant to Qingwan as a one-month-old present.
لقد أعطيت هذه القلادة اليشمية إلى تشينغوان كهدية عندما كان عمرها شهرًا واحدًا.
Remember?
يتذكر؟
On her back,
على ظهرها،
there's a scar from falling off a horse as a kid.
هناك ندبة نتيجة سقوطه من على الحصان عندما كان طفلاً.
Does such a coincidence exist?
هل توجد مثل هذه المصادفة؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
She's our daughter.
إنها ابنتنا.
Mr. Zhao,
السيد تشاو،
what if Boss Huo finds out we acted on our own?
ماذا لو اكتشف الرئيس هيو أننا تصرفنا بمفردنا؟
If he blames us,
إذا لامنا،
I'll take responsibility.
سأتحمل المسؤولية.
Feifei mustn't be harmed today.
لا ينبغي أن يتعرض فيفي للأذى اليوم.
=Episode 3=
=الحلقة 3=
What are you afraid of?
ماذا تخاف منه؟
You're pointing a gun at me.
أنت تصوب مسدسا نحوي.
Of course, I'm scared.
بالطبع أنا خائفة.
I don't believe my daughter would appear out of nowhere.
لا أعتقد أن ابنتي ستظهر من العدم.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What are you plotting?
ماذا تخطط؟
To be honest, I find it hard to believe too.
لأكون صادقًا، أجد صعوبة في تصديق ذلك أيضًا.
I've spent 15 years searching for my parents,
لقد قضيت 15 عامًا في البحث عن والدي،
and suddenly they appear.
وفجأة يظهرون.
I know my place.
أنا أعرف مكاني.
I'm a mere performer.
أنا مجرد مؤدٍ.
How would I dare dream of being a daughter of the Huo family?
كيف يمكنني أن أحلم بأن أكون ابنة عائلة هوو؟
Today,
اليوم،
allow me to perform one last song for First Madam.
اسمحوا لي أن أقدم أغنية أخيرة للسيدة الأولى.
From this day on,
من هذا اليوم فصاعدا،
I'll never set foot in the Huo Residence.
لن أضع قدمي أبدًا في Huo Residence.
Beishan.
بيشان.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll pull the trigger now.
سأسحب الزناد الآن.
If you die,
إذا مت،
I'll accept you as my daughter.
سأقبلك كابنتي.
But if someone rescues you,
ولكن إذا أنقذك شخص ما،
I'll kill you all.
سأقتلكم جميعا.
What's the difference?
ما هو الفرق؟
I have to die anyway.
لا بد أن أموت على أية حال.
Of course there is.
بالطبع هناك.
One will be buried with honors
سيتم دفن أحدهم مع مرتبة الشرف
as a daughter of the Huo family,
باعتبارها ابنة عائلة هوو،
the other will die with no tomb
والآخر سيموت بلا قبر
as a bandit.
كقطاع طرق.
Beishan,
بيشان،
I've been praying every day
لقد كنت أصلي كل يوم
that Qingwan will return.
أن تشينغوان سوف يعود.
I'm begging you.
انا أتوسل إليك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Aunt,
عمة،
today's your birthday.
اليوم عيد ميلادك .
You can't kneel.
لا يمكنك الركوع.
Aunt.
عمة.
Get up.
استيقظ.
First Madam,
سيدتي الأولى،
you don't have to do this for me.
لا يتوجب عليك أن تفعل هذا من أجلي.
In this life,
في هذه الحياة،
our time together may be short.
ربما يكون وقتنا معًا قصيرًا.
In the next,
في القادم،
I hope I can call you mother again.
أتمنى أن أتمكن من مناداتك بأمي مرة أخرى.
Father, I'm so scared.
أبي، أنا خائفة جدًا.
If you're afraid,
إذا كنت خائفا،
pinch your arm.
اضغط على ذراعك.
You won't be scared
لن تخاف
when you feel pain.
عندما تشعر بالألم.
Qingwan.
تشينغوان.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Mother is here.
الأم هنا.
There, there.
هناك، هناك.
Today,
اليوم،
I'll spare you.
سأوفر عليك.
Thank you, Governor.
شكرا لك يا سيدي المحافظ.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Aunt.
عمة.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
I find Miss Yan Qing very interesting.
أجد الآنسة يان تشينغ مثيرة للاهتمام للغاية.
Let her into the Huo Residence for now.
دعوها تدخل إلى مقر هوو في الوقت الحالي.
If she's plotting something,
إذا كانت تخطط لشيء ما،
keeping her close
ابقائها قريبة
is safer.
هو أكثر أمانا.
Good.
جيد.
Keep a close eye on her.
ابقي عينك عليها عن كثب.
Also,
أيضًا،
investigate those people outside.
التحقيق مع هؤلاء الأشخاص في الخارج.
Here.
هنا.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Come on.
تعال.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Get on with your work.
واصل عملك.
Come on.
تعال.
Mr. Zhao,
السيد تشاو،
is Miss Ruan really safe there?
هل السيدة روآن آمنة حقًا هناك؟
(Zhao Xun, Second-in-command of Huofeng Gang) She gave me a signal to leave.
(تشاو شون، الرجل الثاني في قيادة عصابة هووفينج) أعطتني إشارة للمغادرة.
I trust her.
انا اثق بها.
(Huo Residence)
(سكن هوو)
Digging around like this
الحفر حول هذا النحو
will get attention.
سوف تحظى بالاهتمام.
Xiu,
شيو،
I was just
لقد كنت فقط
looking for my jade pendant.
أبحث عن قلادة اليشم الخاصة بي.
It's with me.
إنها معي.
Thank you, Xiu.
شكرا لك، شيو.
Who actually are you?
من أنت في الحقيقة؟
One moment you're Yan Qing,
في لحظة واحدة أنت يان تشينغ،
next you're Huo Qingwan.
التالي أنت هوو تشينغوان.
Xiu,
شيو،
I'm Yan Qing.
أنا يان تشينغ.
But then
ولكن بعد ذلك
I became
لقد أصبحت
the daughter of the Huo family.
ابنة عائلة هوو.
I should get going.
ينبغي لي أن أذهب.
Xiu,
شيو،
undressing a woman you meet
خلع ملابس المرأة التي تقابلها
is rude.
إنه وقح.
Besides,
بجانب،
we're now siblings.
نحن الآن أشقاء.
That's improper,
هذا غير لائق
Xiu.
شيو.
Sorry,
آسف،
Qingwan.
تشينغوان.
I need to take a good look
أحتاج إلى إلقاء نظرة جيدة
at the scar on your back
عند الندبة على ظهرك
and see if it's new
وانظر إذا كان جديدا
or old.
أو قديمة.
Young Marshal Huo who kills without blinking
المارشال الشاب هوو الذي يقتل دون أن يرمش
is shutting his eyes tightly.
يغلق عينيه بإحكام.
Ah, right.
اه، صحيح.
I should thank you.
ينبغي لي أن أشكرك.
If you hadn't helped unzip my clothes
لو لم تساعدني في فتح سحاب ملابسي
and revealed the scar to Mother,
وكشف الندبة للأم،
we wouldn't have recognized each other.
لم نكن لنتعرف على بعضنا البعض.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Did she
هل هي
break into my room yesterday?
اقتحم غرفتي أمس؟
She claimed she wanted her jade pendant back.
قالت أنها تريد استعادة قلادة اليشم الخاصة بها.
I checked her back.
لقد قمت بفحصها مرة أخرى.
It's an old wound.
إنه جرح قديم.
Governor,
محافظ،
Miss Yiyi prepared a bowl of soup for you.
لقد أعدت لك السيدة ييي وعاءً من الحساء.
But I think
ولكنني أعتقد
the scar is new.
الندبة جديدة.
You've worked hard performing outside.
لقد عملت بجد في الأداء بالخارج.
I had the kitchen
كان عندي المطبخ
prepare seafood soup.
تحضير حساء المأكولات البحرية.
It's nourishing.
إنه مغذي.
Yiyi,
ييي،
did you also send some for Governor?
هل أرسلت أيضًا بعضًا منها إلى المحافظ؟
Yes.
نعم.
Uncle, Aunt,
عمي، خالتي،
and Cousin Xiu all received some.
وتلقى ابن عمي شيو بعضًا منها.
So they all know
لذلك كلهم ​​يعرفون
you made it?
هل فعلتها؟
What are you getting at, Qingwan?
ماذا تقصد، تشينغوان؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I just feel bad for you, living in someone else's house
أنا فقط أشعر بالأسف تجاهك، لأنك تعيش في منزل شخص آخر
and always having to be wary of their moods.
ويجب عليهم دائمًا أن يكونوا حذرين من مزاجهم.
It must be hard.
لا بد أن يكون الأمر صعبًا.
Qingwan was allergic to fish and shrimp when she was a kid.
كانت تشينغوان تعاني من حساسية تجاه الأسماك والروبيان عندما كانت طفلة.
Test it on her tomorrow.
اختباره عليها غدا.
What if
ماذا إذا
she's not Qingwan?
انها ليست تشينغوان؟
For those with ill intentions,
بالنسبة لأولئك الذين لديهم نوايا سيئة،
I never spare them.
أنا لا أرحمهم أبدًا.
Drink up, Qingwan.
اشرب، تشينغوان.
The soup is cooling.
الحساء يبرد.
Qingwan.
تشينغوان.
Qingwan!
تشينغوان!
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Uncle.
عم.
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪